<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
		<mods>
		  <li>Cooler Psycasts</li>
		</mods>
		<match Class="PatchOperationSequence">
			<operations>
				<!--level 10-->
				<li Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
					<mods>
					  <li>Anomaly</li>
					</mods>
					<match Class="PatchOperationReplace">
						<xpath>Defs/AbilityDef[defName = "HVP_Voidquake"]/comps/li[@Class="HOP_CoolerPsycasts.CompProperties_AbilityVoidquake"]/incidentDef</xpath>
						<value>
							<incidentDef>UnnaturalDarkness</incidentDef>
						</value>
					</match>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
					<mods>
					  <li>RPG Adventure Flavour Pack</li>
					</mods>
					<match Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
						<mods>
						  <li>Anomaly</li>
						</mods>
						<match Class="PatchOperationReplace">
							<xpath>Defs/AbilityDef[defName = "HVP_Voidquake"]/description</xpath>
							<value>
								<description>Briefly invoke the overwhelming power of the Void. Golems and other constructs will be permanently damaged, living creatures will flee in fear, and unnatural entities will become empowered - unless they are within the safe zone. An unnatural darkness will also descend over the region. Casting this takes 12 seconds of meditation, and afterwards, the caster will go into a five-day coma.\n\nUnlike a mindquake, the effects of a voidquake leave no lasting repercussions on the psyche and do not extend further across the world, so it does not worsen diplomatic relations with other factions.</description>
							</value>
						</match>
						<nomatch Class="PatchOperationReplace">
							<xpath>Defs/AbilityDef[defName = "HVP_Voidquake"]/description</xpath>
							<value>
								<description>Briefly invoke the overwhelming power of the Void. Golems and other constructs will be permanently damaged, and living creatures will flee in fear - unless they are within the safe zone. The very sunlight itself will briefly dim. Casting this takes 12 seconds of meditation, and afterwards, the caster will go into a five-day coma.\n\nUnlike a mindquake, the effects of a voidquake leave no lasting repercussions on the psyche and do not extend further across the world, so it does not worsen diplomatic relations with other factions.</description>
							</value>
						</nomatch>
					</match>
					<nomatch  Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
						<mods>
						  <li>Anomaly</li>
						</mods>
						<match Class="PatchOperationReplace">
							<xpath>Defs/AbilityDef[defName = "HVP_Voidquake"]/description</xpath>
							<value>
								<description>Tear open a brief, localized breach between reality and the Void. Mechanoids will be permanently damaged, living creatures will flee in fear, and unnatural entities will become empowered - unless they are within the safe zone. An unnatural darkness will also descend over the region. Casting this takes 12 seconds of meditation, and afterwards, the caster will go into a five-day psychic coma.\n\nUnlike a neuroquake, the effects of a voidquake leave no lasting repercussions on the psyche and do not extend further across the world, so it does not worsen diplomatic relations with other factions.</description>
							</value>
						</match>
					</nomatch>
				</li>
			</operations>
		</match>
	</Operation>
</Patch>